Aileen Lauren Dautriche.
愛琳 羅倫 多德勒
I want to terminate
我要跟妳…
our engagement.
解除婚約
What?
什麼
Did he say terminate the engagement?
他說解除婚姻
With me?
要跟我解除婚姻
No way.
跟我
No. I remember...
不 我記得…
Somewhere...
好像在哪…
This scene.
這個光景…
I've seen it a few times in my dream.
在夢裡… 看過好幾次…
The crown prince of Elmir Empire,
艾路梅亞王國的皇太子
Cedric Jeanne Elmir.
塞多利克 夏努 艾路梅亞
My fiance.
是我的未婚夫
He is the game's main love interest character.
主要攻略角色…
Main love interest character?
攻略角色
I've decided to live the rest of my life with Lilia.
我已經決定 要跟莉莉安共度一生
Miss Aileen, I'm sorry.
愛琳小姐 對不起
Lilia Rainworth.
莉莉安 雷因華茲
Born a commoner and became the daughter of a baron.
以平民的身份 一躍成為男爵家千金的女孩
The game's heroine.
是遊戲中常見的女主角
Game? Heroine?
遊戲 女主角
I've had enough of your actions and your arrogance.
我受夠妳至今的所作所為 以及傲慢的態度
Aileen.
愛琳
Aileen. Isn't she...
愛琳 她不是…
The heroine's rival.
女主角的情敵
The villainous daughter, Aileen?
反派大小姐愛琳嗎
I finally know what's going on.
我終於弄清楚狀況了
This is the world of a game I'm obsessed with in my previous life.
這裡是我前世時 迷上的遊戲 裡面的世界
Miss Lilia is so pitiful.
莉莉安小姐好可憐
I heard she was being ordered to not greet other people.
聽說她命令人家 不准先打招呼
Giving orders at the academy soiree.
在學園祭時 對人家頤指氣使的
I remember this scene. It's the "Engagement Termination" event.
我記得這一幕 是遊戲中的解除婚約事件
I was being tricked.
我被暗算了
Since you won't listen to my explanation, I'll be taking my leave then.
看來您不願意聽我解釋 那我就先告辭了
I'm not crying as you had hoped
無法讓您見到我哭泣的模樣
-so it's really a pity. -I have to smile.
我深感遺憾 我要笑
I can't let them feel like they have the upper hand.
不讓對方感到一絲一毫的優越感
Lord Cedric.
塞多利克大人
I used to admire you.
我曾仰慕過您
This is the world of the Otome game, "Regalia of Saints, Demons and Maidens".
這裡是乙女遊戲 聖與魔與少女的雷加利亞裡的世界
The heroine, Lilia, is the legendary Holy Sword Maiden.
女主角莉莉安 是傳說中的聖劍少女
She will have a battle with the awakened Demon King.
將與覺醒後的魔王對決
VILLAINOUS DAUGHTER, AILEEN
(反派大小姐愛琳…)
Meanwhile, Aileen's endings
而愛琳…
"DEATH" are all deaths in ridiculous ways.
(死亡) 最後的結局卻很悽慘…
Even if I die a cruel death in the game,
就算在遊戲中死得很慘
I can't die in real life.
我也不能在這現實中死去
Think. Remember.
仔細想 快想起來
What I can do in this situation is...
在這個情況下我能做的是…
The key to a Bad End is the awakening of the Demon King.
迎來BD的關鍵是魔王覺醒
So,
那麼…
to stop him from awakening,
要阻止他覺醒
I have to keep the Last Boss!
就只能飼養最終大魔王了
I'M A VILLAINOUS DAUGHTER, SO I'M GOING TO KEEP THE LAST BOSS!
《因為是反派大小姐》 《所以養了魔王》
THE VILLAINOUS DAUGHTER RAISES THE CURTAIN
(反派大小姐揭開序幕)
It's full of bad omens.
衰運連連…
Human, turn back.
人類 滾回去
The girl who got her engagement terminated.
被解除婚約的小丫頭
So many bad things have been said about you.
妳的評價爛透了
Capricious. Arrogant.
任性 傲慢
Simply humiliating others. Is that how you treat your guests?
莫名其妙的侮辱他人 就是你們的待客之道嗎
I am Aileen Lauren Dautriche.
我是愛琳 羅倫 多德勒
I have no intention to leave before I see your master.
見到你們的君主之前 我絕不回去
I've inherited the blood of the Holy Sword Maiden after all.
好歹 我也繼承了聖劍少女的血脈
This is nothing to me.
這點小事根本不算什麼
Let me help you.
我幫妳吧
Thanks for your help...
謝謝你的幫…
Hold on...
慢著…
This is far more potent than the still drawing in the game.
比遊戲中的繪圖還要魄力十足
How disgustingly gorgeous!
令人憎恨的美貌
What does a human want with me?
人類找我何事
You must be Claude Jeanne Elmir.
你就是 庫洛德 夏努 艾路梅亞大人吧
That's right.
沒錯
I think this is a good deal.
我想這應該是個不錯的交易
I want you
跟我…
to marry me!
結婚吧
You would like
妳說…
who to marry whom?
誰跟誰結婚
I am the youngest daughter of a duke.
我是公爵家的么女
I was born into a loving family.
在眾人寵愛中成長
However, I'm a girl who is not as excellent as my brothers.
然而因為我是女孩 不如哥哥們那般優秀
I couldn't catch up with my brothers no matter how hard I worked.
就算我再怎麼努力 也追趕不上哥哥們
So, I've always thought I am worthless.
所以我一直認為 自己沒有存在的價值
When I was eight years old, Prince Cedric proposed to me.
八歲時 塞多利克王子跟我求婚
It was my first time being relied upon.
那是我初次被賦予期待
Becoming the empress became Aileen's dream.
當上王妃便成為愛琳的夢想
To become an amazing empress,
為了成為了不起的王妃
perhaps I've worked too hard.
或許是太過努力了
When I realised,
等到我發覺時
I was already referred to as an arrogant woman because I'm the crown prince's fiancee.
已被大家視為以皇太子未婚妻身份 耀武揚威的傲慢大小姐
I should have presented myself as a cute and delicate girl.
早知道就表現得 更楚楚可憐的模樣…
Would things have been different?
待遇是否會有點不同呢
The Demon King wasn't angry.
魔王沒有生氣
The thunder was caused by his shock.
只是因震驚而落下那道雷
He didn't... Get angry?
他沒有…生氣…
Indeed.
也是
If Master Claude gets angry, there will be a catastrophe.
庫洛德大人真動怒的話 可是會釀成災害的
Why are you taking care of him?
魔王為何要照顧她
I had no choice.
我並無他意
-Did she propose to you, Master Claude? -I remember he has two close advisors.
-她向庫洛德大人求婚了嗎 -我記得他有兩位親信
Their names are Keith
名叫吉斯…
-and the demon, Belzebuth. -Are you planning to nurse this girl?
-和魔物佩魯賽博特 -王打算豢養這個小丫頭嗎
I don't plan to do that.
無此打算
She might have received someone's orders.
她或許是受到某人的命令
This might be a trap.
可能是個圈套
No.
不是的
I came here of my own free will.
我是自願來此的
Claude Jeanne Elmir.
庫洛德 夏努 艾路梅亞
Cedric's half-brother.
塞多利克的異母兄弟
He was discovered to be a demon when he was 10 years old.
10歲時被發現是魔物
The humans stripped his right to inherit the throne.
人們剝奪了他的王位繼承權
The demons and humans formed a non-aggression pact
魔物和人類締結非戰公約
and he was banished to the abandoned castle.
他則被放逐在廢棄城堡中
If his hatred for the humans has been awakened,
若他對人類的憎恨覺醒
he will transform into the final boss dragon that kills Aileen.
就會化身為最終大魔王的惡龍 並殺死愛琳
To avoid this Bad End...
為了避免迎接悲慘結局
Marry me! I'll give you happiness!
跟我結婚吧 我會讓你幸福的
Throw her out.
趕出去
I'll return immediately if you agree to my proposal.
只要你答應我的求婚 我就馬上回去
It's our first meeting.
我們才第一次見面
Why are you proposing to me?
為何跟我求婚
It's because... Well...
是因為…那個…
Do you like me?
妳… 喜歡我嗎
No.
不是
Master Claude! No tornados, please!
庫洛德大人 請別颳起龍捲風
After having your engagement terminated by Cedric,
妳被塞多利克解除婚約後
how can you still...
竟然還有臉…
This is my last resort.
我也有不得已的原因
I don't want to cry my whole life.
但我也不能以淚洗面過日子
I don't want to waste a single second of my life.
我不想浪費人生的一分一秒
So, you came to seduce the Demon King?
所以妳就來搭訕魔王
Seduce...
搭訕…
Yes. Seducing a man is easy for me...
是啊 對我來說 搭訕男人是輕而易舉的…
I apologise for my appearance.
我這身不得體的模樣 讓你見笑了
I'll return when I've dressed appropriately.
我重新打扮後再來
There's no need for that.
無妨
There's no reason for you to return.
這樣你就不用再來了
Get lost.
滾
I will cherish it.
我會好好珍惜的
A dress enchanted with magic. It's amazing!
施了魔法的洋裝 好棒喔
Is this magic as well?
這也是魔法嗎
Get lost!
快滾
He forced me back using magic?
他用魔法強制送我回來
He got me.
被擺了一道
Aileen, you seem to be doing better than I expected.
愛琳 妳比我想得還要有精神
I am so disappointed.
可是爸爸好失望
This sadist father.
這個裝抖S的爸爸
It's quite shocking to see that this is the true personality of the empire's prime minister.
真令人驚訝王國主宰一切的宰相 真面目是這樣…
We received an invitation from Lord Cedric and Miss Lilia.
我們收到塞多利克大人 和莉莉安小姐給的邀請函
They will announce their engagement at the banquet two months later.
兩個月後的晚宴上 發表婚約
You have to sign the document to terminate your engagement in public.
而妳要在眾人面前 簽下解除婚約的文件
Dumping me once again in public?
在公開場合上 再次甩掉我嗎
What do you plan to do?
妳有什麼打算
Miss Lilia even included a handwritten letter.
莉莉安小姐還特地親手附上信件
I will attend it.
我會出席
I'll accept anyone's challenge.
誰來挑釁我 我就奉陪到底
I still need Master Claude's help no matter what.
還是得拉攏庫洛德大人
2 KILOMETRES TO THE DEMON KING'S CASTLE
(距離魔王城還有2公里)
I've been walking around in circles!
從剛才我就一直繞來繞去的
Is it because of the barrier?
因為有結界的關係嗎
What a pity!
真可惜
I even prepared some sweets as an apology.
我特地帶了點心來賠罪呢
Also.
還有
How you treat your guests will affect your Master's reputation.
迎賓的好壞 會影響主人的評價
The one responsible should wear this.
負責人 戴上這個
A gatekeeper's proof.
做為守門人的證明
Gatekeeper's proof?
守門人的證明
Child!
小丫頭
Give that to me!
把證明給我
It suits you.
好適合你喔
Please try some if you don't mind.
不嫌棄的話 也請嚐嚐
I want almond.
我要杏仁
Delicious.
好吃…
What's going on?
怎麼回事…
I laced it with a paralysis drug.
我放了麻痺身體的藥物
I didn't expect you to trust humans.
沒想到你這麼相信人類
How foolish.
真蠢
Is this what a human would say?
這是人類會說的台詞嗎
Well then, Master Claude! Come out at once!
好了庫洛德大人 快出來吧
Otherwise, I'll pluck all the feathers off this demon...
不然我就拔掉這隻魔物的羽毛
and turn it into a bald crow!
讓牠變成禿鴉
Bald crow?
禿鴉
Good day, Master Claude.
庫洛德大人您好
Please heal it.
請治好牠吧
Child, I'll kill you! I'll definitely kill you!
小丫頭 殺了妳 我要殺了妳
You were the one who slandered me yesterday.
誰叫你昨天污衊我
We are even now.
我們扯平了
I will no longer be fooled!
我不會再被騙了
Don't worry.
別擔心
Only the ones with almonds are laced with the drug.
有杏仁的才摻了麻痺藥
There's nothing wrong with it.
沒問題
Delicious. Chocolate is delicious!
好吃 巧克力好吃
Oh no. What should I do?
怎麼辦 居然會這樣…
Did you put something in this as well?
難道 裡面也加了什麼嗎
Yes. I want to put Master Claude in the mood for "that"
是的 因為我想讓庫洛德大人 有"那方面"的意願
and added a love potion.
所以加了媚藥
You are so weird.
妳太奇怪了吧
Actually, I need to attend a banquet two months from now.
是這樣的 我要出席兩個月後的晚宴
I want Master Claude to be my escort.
請庫洛德大人務必陪同
Why did you use a love potion then?
那妳幹嘛下媚藥
Because you might not listen to me if I had requested nicely.
因為我好好拜託你 你可能不會乖乖聽話
So, I want you to do something that cannot be undone.
所以只好先讓生米煮成熟飯
Demon King!
魔王大人…
Almond.
杏仁
Don't simply name me as you wish!
別擅自幫我取名字
Ignore her. What is it?
別理她 怎麼了
Ran outside the forest!
跑到森林外
Fenrir's child.
芬里爾的小孩
It escaped to the second layer in the east.
跑出去的地方 是東邊第二層
It has exceeded the barrier's limit.
已經超過結界的範圍
That's the academy's direction.
是往學園的方向
I can't imagine what will happen if the students see it.
不知道被學生們發現後會怎麼樣
I'll go and find it.
我去找
If humans see you, it will cause a commotion, Belzebuth.
佩魯賽博特被人類看到的話 更會引起騷動的
I'm going.
我去吧
I know the layout of the academy well.
我很清楚學園的地理位置
Even if it's a child, it is still a Fenrir.
就算只是小孩 但那還是芬里爾
It might bite you to death.
妳可能會被牠咬死的
In that case, lend this to me.
那麼 這個借我吧
Demons should be able to identify your scent.
魔物應該分辨得出味道
Why? There's no need to help us.
為什麼 妳沒必要幫這個忙
I feel bad for the poor lost child.
因為迷路的小孩很可憐
Of course, I also want Master Claude to owe me a favour.
當然也打算賣你一個人情
So, that's your plan...
原來妳有這個打算…
I want to grant your wish.
我想實現你的願望
I'm counting on you.
拜託妳了
I'm counting on you?
拜託我了…
It feels good to be relied on.
被拜託的感覺真不錯
I have to help the lost child.
我得好好幫忙 迷路的小孩
I'M A VILLAINOUS DAUGHTER, SO I'M GOING TO KEEP THE LAST BOSS!
《因為是反派大小姐》 《所以養了魔王》
AILEEN LAUREN DAUTRICHE CV, RIE TAKAHASHI
(愛琳 羅倫 多德勒) (CV 高橋李依)
THE MOST POWERFUL NOBLE FAMILY IN ELMIR EMPIRE. BARON DAUTRICHE'S ONLY DAUGHTER.
(艾路梅亞王國 勢力最龐大貴族) (多德勒公爵家的獨生女)
HER FATHER IS THE PRIME MINISTER. HER MOTHER IS THE EMPRESS DOWAGER'S NIECE.
(父親是宰相) (母親是皇太后的姪女)
RESPECTED BY SOCIAL AND MILITARY CLASSES. DUCHESS.
(受到社交界和軍隊尊敬的) (公爵夫人)
HAS ROYAL BLOOD, INHERITED THE HOLY SWORD MAIDEN'S BLOOD.
(有皇族血脈) (繼承聖劍少女的血緣)
Great!
很好
Aim for its head!
瞄準牠的頭
Do it while it's trapped.
趁他被陷阱困住 快動手
If we kill it, joining the Holy Knights will no longer be a dream.
打死牠 加入聖騎士團 就不再是夢想了
Are you trying to kill a demon?
你們打算殺死魔物嗎
Haven't you heard of the non-aggression pact?
沒聽過非戰公約嗎
Miss Aileen?
愛琳小姐
Weren't you expelled from the academy?
妳不是被退學了嗎
Nice to meet you. I am Aileen.
初次見面你好 我是愛琳
I'm here to pick you up.
我來接你了
What are you doing?
你們幹什麼
We can't let the demon escape!
不能讓魔物逃走
I said stop it!
我叫你們住手
The parent came out of the barrier to find its child?
家長穿過結界來找小孩了
No roaring. You will attract the humans.
別叫 會把人類引來
Hurry.
快走
Aileen!
愛琳
Lord Cedric.
塞多利克大人
I received reports of you harming demons and planning to attack Lilia.
我收到妳傷害魔物 並打算襲擊莉莉安的報告
Do you think I'm someone who will come up with such a silly plan?
你覺得那種蠢計畫是我想的嗎
It's highly possible for you.
妳很可能這麼做
Wait.
等等
I don't think Miss Aileen will do that,
我覺得愛琳小姐不會這麼做
Lord Cedric.
塞多利克大人
I'll forgive you today because of Lilia.
今天就看在莉莉安的分上饒了妳
Leave this place now.
快點離開
But Miss Aileen is hurt...
可是愛琳小姐受傷了…
She deserved that. She can crawl home.
這是她自作自受 自己想辦法爬回去吧
Marcus, let's go.
馬庫斯 走吧
Poor thing.
可憐啊
It doesn't hurt me at all.
我不覺得心痛
I no longer care about my reputation...
我早就不在意別人的眼光…
Brother?
兄長大人
Demon King?
魔王
He shouldn't be leaving the forest.
他應該不會離開森林啊
Brother, why are you here?
兄長大人 為何來這裡…
Aileen Lauren Dautriche.
愛琳 羅倫 多德勒
Yes.
是
I'm here to thank you.
我是來向妳道謝的
You did not fear the child of Fenrir
妳不畏懼芬里爾之子
and rescued it.
並伸出援手救助牠
You are willing to take the blame
為了避免人類與魔物引發爭執
to avoid a conflict between demons and humans.
願意忍氣吞聲背黑鍋
As the Demon King,
我身為魔王
I sincerely thank you.
衷心感謝妳
He is here to save me...
他是來救我的…
Helping me to clear my name.
幫我洗刷冤屈
It doesn't benefit you even if you do that.
就算你這麼做 也得不到任何好處啊
Let me send you back.
我送妳回去吧
Where did that come from?
從哪變出來的
It's too early to be startled.
現在就驚訝還太早了
It's so pretty.
好漂亮
You look like a normal girl from a noble family.
看起來 就像普通的千金小姐
Excuse me. I am indeed a normal girl from a noble family.
真失禮 我真的是普通的千金小姐
I already know you are someone who doesn't find excuses, seek help and cry easily.
我已經知道 妳是個不輕易落淚 不找藉口也不尋求幫助的人
That is why you won't tell me the reason for your proposal.
所以才不告訴我求婚的原因
Because you won't believe me even if I tell you.
因為我覺得就算我說了 你也不會相信
That's not for you to decide.
這點不是由妳來決定
I'll tell you then.
那我就說了
Actually, this world
其實這個世界
is an Otome game I played in my previous life.
是前世的我在玩的乙女遊戲
I'm the villainous daughter in the game.
我是遊戲中的反派大小姐
I will be killed by Lord Claude who turns into an evil dragon.
會被變成惡龍的庫洛德大人殺死
I see. I understand now.
原來如此 我懂了
You are fooling around with me.
妳在耍我
No way!
不會吧
I'm going to die?
要死了
A meteor?
流星
What are you doing?
你幹什麼啦
What's the meaning of this?
這是什麼意思…
I will attend the banquet.
我會出席晚宴
Then, we'll be even
這樣我們就扯平
and your wish will be granted.
也如妳所願了
That's true.
是沒錯啦
But why...
但為什麼…
Are you smiling?
你在笑呢
Because
因為
I want to see you cry.
我想看妳哭泣的臉龐
Can I escape my fate
這樣我是否能…
of dying a cruel death in the end?
稍微遠離慘死的結局呢